{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854870332","data":{"timestamp":" 946854870332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854871373","data":{"timestamp":" 946854871373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854873940","data":{"timestamp":" 946854873940"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854874981","data":{"timestamp":" 946854874981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854877865","data":{"timestamp":" 946854877865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854878916","data":{"timestamp":" 946854878916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854881769","data":{"timestamp":" 946854881769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854883560","data":{"timestamp":" 946854883560"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854885918","data":{"timestamp":" 946854885918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854886964","data":{"timestamp":" 946854886964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854889652","data":{"timestamp":" 946854889652"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854889858","data":{"timestamp":" 946854889858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854890741","data":{"timestamp":" 946854890741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854893061","data":{"timestamp":" 946854893060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854895444","data":{"timestamp":" 946854895444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854897094","data":{"timestamp":" 946854897094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854899679","data":{"timestamp":" 946854899679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854900737","data":{"timestamp":" 946854900737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854903999","data":{"timestamp":" 946854903999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854905039","data":{"timestamp":" 946854905039"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854907841","data":{"timestamp":" 946854907841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854908869","data":{"timestamp":" 946854908869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854912038","data":{"timestamp":" 946854912038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854912394","data":{"timestamp":" 946854912394"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854913194","data":{"timestamp":" 946854913194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854915888","data":{"timestamp":" 946854915888"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854918697","data":{"timestamp":" 946854918697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854918724","data":{"timestamp":" 946854918723"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854930594","data":{"timestamp":" 946854930593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854930693","data":{"timestamp":" 946854930693"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 17a7e350-0efc-432f-916c-51c26620fa6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854978848","data":{"timestamp":" 946854978848"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_maji-hii-maji-moto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854981570","data":{"timestamp":" 946854981570"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_maji-hii-maji-moto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" hii"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854984668","data":{"timestamp":" 946854984668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_maji-hii-maji-moto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946854987851","data":{"timestamp":" 946854987851"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_maji-hii-maji-moto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" moto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855006737","data":{"timestamp":" 946855006737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_wanaume-usiku-baada-hata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" wanaume"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855009417","data":{"timestamp":" 946855009417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_wanaume-usiku-baada-hata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" usiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855029262","data":{"timestamp":" 946855029262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nta_nta-ngozi-hizi-ukweli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nta"," userResponse":" nta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855053622","data":{"timestamp":" 946855053622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchana_tawi-mchana-malishoni-uko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchana"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855056367","data":{"timestamp":" 946855056367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchana_tawi-mchana-malishoni-uko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchana"," userResponse":" mchana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855090320","data":{"timestamp":" 946855090320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali_samahani-kali-tatu-tatu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" samahani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855092994","data":{"timestamp":" 946855092994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali_samahani-kali-tatu-tatu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855124563","data":{"timestamp":" 946855124562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_macho-ndege-kubwa-kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" macho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855127226","data":{"timestamp":" 946855127226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_macho-ndege-kubwa-kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855147571","data":{"timestamp":" 946855147569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ndege_macho-ndege-kubwa-kuku"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855147719","data":{"timestamp":" 946855147719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ace07662-c2af-4c30-b383-070b741a14a3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855167066","data":{"timestamp":" 946855167065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855169176","data":{"timestamp":" 946855169175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855171337","data":{"timestamp":" 946855171337"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855174570","data":{"timestamp":" 946855174570"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855176841","data":{"timestamp":" 946855176841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855179105","data":{"timestamp":" 946855179105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855181963","data":{"timestamp":" 946855181962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855184167","data":{"timestamp":" 946855184167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855186375","data":{"timestamp":" 946855186375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855189717","data":{"timestamp":" 946855189717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855191820","data":{"timestamp":" 946855191820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855193946","data":{"timestamp":" 946855193946"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855196983","data":{"timestamp":" 946855196982"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855199260","data":{"timestamp":" 946855199259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855201506","data":{"timestamp":" 946855201505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855204566","data":{"timestamp":" 946855204565"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855206906","data":{"timestamp":" 946855206906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855209252","data":{"timestamp":" 946855209252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855212306","data":{"timestamp":" 946855212306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855214396","data":{"timestamp":" 946855214396"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855216537","data":{"timestamp":" 946855216537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855219672","data":{"timestamp":" 946855219672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855221871","data":{"timestamp":" 946855221871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855224077","data":{"timestamp":" 946855224076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855227270","data":{"timestamp":" 946855227269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855229684","data":{"timestamp":" 946855229683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855232107","data":{"timestamp":" 946855232107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855235279","data":{"timestamp":" 946855235278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855237562","data":{"timestamp":" 946855237562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855239829","data":{"timestamp":" 946855239828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855242851","data":{"timestamp":" 946855242851"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855245065","data":{"timestamp":" 946855245065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855247273","data":{"timestamp":" 946855247273"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855250259","data":{"timestamp":" 946855250258"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855252666","data":{"timestamp":" 946855252666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855255064","data":{"timestamp":" 946855255063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855258198","data":{"timestamp":" 946855258197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855260595","data":{"timestamp":" 946855260595"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855262895","data":{"timestamp":" 946855262895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855265906","data":{"timestamp":" 946855265906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855268174","data":{"timestamp":" 946855268173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855270474","data":{"timestamp":" 946855270473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855273824","data":{"timestamp":" 946855273823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855276077","data":{"timestamp":" 946855276077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855278360","data":{"timestamp":" 946855278360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855281707","data":{"timestamp":" 946855281705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855284166","data":{"timestamp":" 946855284165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855286661","data":{"timestamp":" 946855286660"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855289505","data":{"timestamp":" 946855289505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855291682","data":{"timestamp":" 946855291682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855293875","data":{"timestamp":" 946855293874"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855297354","data":{"timestamp":" 946855297353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855299675","data":{"timestamp":" 946855299674"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855301996","data":{"timestamp":" 946855301996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855305154","data":{"timestamp":" 946855305153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855307451","data":{"timestamp":" 946855307450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855309763","data":{"timestamp":" 946855309762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855312741","data":{"timestamp":" 946855312741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855314835","data":{"timestamp":" 946855314835"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855317028","data":{"timestamp":" 946855317025"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855320164","data":{"timestamp":" 946855320164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855322435","data":{"timestamp":" 946855322435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855324643","data":{"timestamp":" 946855324643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855327804","data":{"timestamp":" 946855327803"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855330050","data":{"timestamp":" 946855330049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855332323","data":{"timestamp":" 946855332323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855335607","data":{"timestamp":" 946855335606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855337967","data":{"timestamp":" 946855337967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855340320","data":{"timestamp":" 946855340319"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855343474","data":{"timestamp":" 946855343474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855345849","data":{"timestamp":" 946855345848"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855348173","data":{"timestamp":" 946855348173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855351608","data":{"timestamp":" 946855351607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855351705","data":{"timestamp":" 946855351705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 5d6904e0-8b7a-497a-9ef7-30d796406a22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855398619","data":{"timestamp":" 946855398619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855406747","data":{"timestamp":" 946855406747"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855414204","data":{"timestamp":" 946855414204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855421017","data":{"timestamp":" 946855421017"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855428829","data":{"timestamp":" 946855428829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855435711","data":{"timestamp":" 946855435711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855443927","data":{"timestamp":" 946855443926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855449988","data":{"timestamp":" 946855449988"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855459313","data":{"timestamp":" 946855459313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855465201","data":{"timestamp":" 946855465201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855473611","data":{"timestamp":" 946855473611"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855482540","data":{"timestamp":" 946855482539"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855491038","data":{"timestamp":" 946855491038"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855497939","data":{"timestamp":" 946855497938"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855506019","data":{"timestamp":" 946855506019"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855514291","data":{"timestamp":" 946855514291"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855523484","data":{"timestamp":" 946855523484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855549394","data":{"timestamp":" 946855549394"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855569371","data":{"timestamp":" 946855569371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ed979c45-0498-492e-9c0f-3106c74a91b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855580266","data":{"timestamp":" 946855580266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855590278","data":{"timestamp":" 946855590278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855591838","data":{"timestamp":" 946855591838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855595165","data":{"timestamp":" 946855595165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855596725","data":{"timestamp":" 946855596725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855602328","data":{"timestamp":" 946855602328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855603918","data":{"timestamp":" 946855603917"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855608836","data":{"timestamp":" 946855608836"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855610445","data":{"timestamp":" 946855610445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855619183","data":{"timestamp":" 946855619183"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855620779","data":{"timestamp":" 946855620778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855638845","data":{"timestamp":" 946855638845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855640478","data":{"timestamp":" 946855640478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855645501","data":{"timestamp":" 946855645501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855647074","data":{"timestamp":" 946855647074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855651813","data":{"timestamp":" 946855651812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855653441","data":{"timestamp":" 946855653441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855657305","data":{"timestamp":" 946855657305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855658868","data":{"timestamp":" 946855658868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855662364","data":{"timestamp":" 946855662364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855663924","data":{"timestamp":" 946855663924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855667574","data":{"timestamp":" 946855667574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855669586","data":{"timestamp":" 946855669585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855669754","data":{"timestamp":" 946855669754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" 74e5e406-d654-4087-85bf-88cbb12340e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855681079","data":{"timestamp":" 946855681078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855685978","data":{"timestamp":" 946855685977"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855687570","data":{"timestamp":" 946855687570"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855691154","data":{"timestamp":" 946855691153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855692738","data":{"timestamp":" 946855692738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855700436","data":{"timestamp":" 946855700436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855702003","data":{"timestamp":" 946855702003"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855706424","data":{"timestamp":" 946855706424"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855707997","data":{"timestamp":" 946855707996"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855712775","data":{"timestamp":" 946855712774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855714361","data":{"timestamp":" 946855714361"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855719292","data":{"timestamp":" 946855719292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855720865","data":{"timestamp":" 946855720865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855724892","data":{"timestamp":" 946855724892"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855726508","data":{"timestamp":" 946855726508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855728269","data":{"timestamp":" 946855728269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855729829","data":{"timestamp":" 946855729828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855765498","data":{"timestamp":" 946855765497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855765749","data":{"timestamp":" 946855765749"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" ef61d8d4-365a-44d2-aec0-6bdc1b4f9e03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855806046","data":{"timestamp":" 946855806046"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tule_tule-gari-refu-popote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tule"," userResponse":" tule"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855845830","data":{"timestamp":" 946855845830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchoyo_mchoyo-tuli-makao-sanduku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchoyo"," userResponse":" mchoyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855882846","data":{"timestamp":" 946855882845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makali_makali-mate-kamili-umbali"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" makali"," userResponse":" makali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855919667","data":{"timestamp":" 946855919667"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-yule-hadi-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855922425","data":{"timestamp":" 946855922424"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-yule-hadi-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" yule"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855927548","data":{"timestamp":" 946855927547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-yule-hadi-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855930271","data":{"timestamp":" 946855930271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-yule-hadi-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855952188","data":{"timestamp":" 946855952188"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo_chako-pembe-mpira-tumbo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tumbo"," userResponse":" tumbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855979685","data":{"timestamp":" 946855979684"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama_mama-za-nyumba-mtoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855993070","data":{"timestamp":" 946855993068"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mama_mama-za-nyumba-mtoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946855993216","data":{"timestamp":" 946855993216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856014087","data":{"timestamp":" 946856014087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_021417"," gameId":" c75362f1-76d2-4e66-a049-aeff9d369931"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}